
Estrellita Espero 
Administrative Assistant 
    
One Mid America Plaza, Suite 900
Oakbrook Terrace, IL 60181
P 630.954.3279 F 630.954.3701 Mailing address: 
1645 W. Jackson Blvd., Suite 501
Chicago, IL 60612-6376 CONFIDENTIALITY NOTICE: This communication is intended only for the use of the individual(s) or entity designated by the sender as the recipient. This communication may contain information which is confidential, and in certain instances, privileged, under applicable law. If you are not the intended recipient as designated by the sender, or such recipient’s authorized agent, you are hereby notified that any dissemination, copy, or disclosure of this communication beyond the intended recipient is strictly prohibited. 


